Curriculum Vitae

Tomasz Maksim

phone: 083 309 3550

e-mail: tomaszmaksim@gmail.com



Personal Profile:

Front-end developer also experienced in customer focused environment. Friendly and polite with excellent understanding of quality customer service. Very reliable and flexible with excellent organisational skills.

I am constantly updating my IT skills, currently I'm learning programming using JavaScript and React.

Key skills:

Computer skills: JAVA 8, HTML 5, CSS, MySQL, Bootstrap, Adobe Illustrator & Photoshop, Figma, Microsoft Office, Gant Project Management, Balsamic Mockups.

Excellent communication and interpersonal skills.

Technical problem solving skills.

Attention to detail.

Project management skills and efficient team-player.

Strong organizational and analytical skills.

Languages: Fluent English and Polish, basic German.

Additional Training:

Full cat. B driving license, CompTIA Cloud Essentials, Google Analytics, HACCP, Manual Handling, Payback - payroll software.

Education and qualifications:

| 09.2020 - present | JavaScript and React Creative online course |
|-------------------|--|
| 2020 - 08.2020 | Programming using HTML & CSS online course |
| 2019 - 05.2019 | Adobe Certified Associate online course |
| 2017 - 05.2018 | JAVA 8 Software Developer Course, Cenit College Naas |
| 2016 | Multi Digital Skills Course, Cenit College Naas |
| 1999 - 2001 | Management and Marketing College in Wroclaw, Poland |
| 1999 | Secondary School Leaving examination |
| | |

Career History:

Dec 2018 – present Self-employed, Magic Mirror photo-booth & Chocolate fountains rental for the events, Web Design

Responsibilities:

Daily customer service

Design and implementation of the templates for the Magic Mirror photo-booth

Creation of the websites

Responsibility for social media advertisement

Invoicina

Deliveries and collections of the rented equipment

Equipment maintenance and troubleshooting

Jan 2010 - Sep 2016

Self-employed, Hussar, European Grocery Stores

Responsibilities:

Daily customer service

Electrical and refrigeration on-site devices troubleshooting, maintenance and service

Supervision of the employees

Coordination of the shipments

Stock control management

Production of accounts, payroll and rosters

Design and execution of marketing campaigns

Training of staff Stock deliveries

Dec 2007 - Dec 2008

Hewlett-Packard Leixlip, Co.Kildare

Role: Assembly line operator

Responsibilities:

Monitoring work of ink cartridges assembly line

Responsible for quality of products Maintained stock levels of materials Small technical issues troubleshooting

Performing with engineers experiments and tests

Jan 2007 - Dec 2007

IBM Damastown, Dublin Warehouse employee

Role:

Responsibilities:

Collecting orders for IBM's customers

Team member of quality team responsible for orders inspections

Mar 2006- Dec 2006

St. Jameses Hospital Dublin

Role:

Security Officer

Responsibilities:

Providing security for patients and staff on the hospital grounds and A&E

2001 - 2005

Maxima Ladies clothes retail shop

Role:

Sales Assistant

Responsibilities:

Providing excellent customer experience

Cashier responsibilities Deliveries management

Interests:

Books, movies and sports.

References:

Delighted to supply upon request.

Tomasz Maksim CV page 2